[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I'm not sure",
    "front": "Ich bin mir nicht Sicher",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "are you available tomorrow?",
    "front": "Sind Sie morgen verfügbar?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "What did you do yesterday?",
    "front": "Was hast du gestern gemacht?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "What are you doing there?",
    "front": "was machst Du da?",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "let's go to the cantine",
    "front": "Lass uns die Cantine gehen",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "that's not right",
    "front": "Das ist nicht richtig",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },

  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "What do you like to do?",
    "front": "Was möchten Sie tun?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I can't see it",
    "front": "Ich sehe es nicht",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "My friend is with Gianni",
    "front": "Die Mutter is bei dem Gianni",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },

  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Have a nice day",
    "front": "Eine schöner Tag noch",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I feel really good today",
    "front": "Mir geht ist Heute sehr gut",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I have to go",
    "front": "Ich muss gehen",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Why are you late?",
    "front": "Warum bist du zu spät?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Sorry for being late",
    "front": "Es tut mir leid daß ist zu spät bin",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I have to go to the gym",
    "front": "Ich muss ins Fitnessstudio",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Can we meet next week?",
    "front": "Können wir uns nächste Woche treffen?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "How was your Journey?",
    "front": "Wie war Ihre Reise?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Have fun",
    "front": "Viel Späß",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "just a minute, please",
    "front": "Nur eine Minute bitte",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "are you ready",
    "front": "Bist du bereit?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I have no idea",
    "front": "Keine Ahnung!",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Where do you live?",
    "front": "Wo lebst du?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Do you work as Veterinarian?",
    "front": "Arbeitest du nicht als Ärztin?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I'm planning to stay at home",
    "front": "Ich habe vor, zu Hause zu bleiben",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I'm free tomorrow",
    "front": "Ich bin morgen frei",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "I need more time off",
    "front": "Ich brauche mehr Urlaub",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "wahrscheinlich hast du recht",
    "front": "You are probably right",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "It doesn't matter",
    "front": "das ist egal",
    "tags": []
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "back": "Keine Eile",
    "front": "No rush (no hay apuro)",
    "tags": []
  }
]
